{
    "question": "You....... an old table\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>You....... an old table\u200b</p><p>You <strong>have </strong>an old table.</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Jawaban pada kalimat di atas dicetak tebal dan merupakan bentuk Simple Present Tense karena menjelaskan fakta. Jika subjek nya adalah kata You, maka harus memakai kata kerja Have yang artinya memiliki.</p><p>Semoga membantu ya.</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "besi-tanah-udara-merupakan-contoh-962",
            "question": "Besi tanah udara merupakan contoh\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>benda yang dapat di perbarui</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf jika salah:)</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1-i-like-to-play-football-my-father-also-likes-to-play-football-735",
            "question": "1. I like to play football. My father also likes to play football !    2. Tigers are found in Sumatera. They are also found in Java!\r\n3. When it rains, people stay home. People going to the shopping mall!\r\n4. My mother, my father went to university!\r\n5. We learn speak English in our class. We speak English in our home!\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>1. I and my father like to play football</p><p>2. Tigers are found in Sumatera and Java</p><p>3. </p><p>4.</p><p>5. We speak English in class and at home.</p><p></p><p>Penjelasan: </p><p>hope you find this helpful^\u2022^</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "choose-the-correct-answer-by-crossing-abc-or-d-ana-edi-the-fol-783",
            "question": "Choose the correct answer by crossing a,b,c or d!    Ana\r\nEdi\r\nThe following conversation is used to answer questions number 1-5\r\n: This park is shadyand the flowers are colorful.I (1).....this park\r\n: I do,too. This is a (2).....park\r\nMono : Look!There are butterflies.\r\n: They are(3) ....\r\n: There are garbage cans too. We can keep this park(4).\r\nEni\r\n: I like studying here. The weather is nice. The park is beautiful.\r\nAnd it's a (5)......\r\nPutri\r\nAdi\r\n@@@\r\n1. a. want to go\r\nb. hate\r\nc. like\r\nd. feel\r\n2. a. ugly\r\nb. dirty\r\nc. city\r\nd. wonderful\r\n3. a. flyng\r\nb. boring\r\nc. pretty\r\nd. dirty\r\n4. a. dirty\r\nb. clean\r\nc. ugly\r\nd. wonderful\r\n5. a. terrible\r\nb. horrible\r\nc. beautiful\r\nd. pret\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. C. Like</p><p>2.  D. Wonderful</p><p>3. C. Pretty</p><p>4. B. Clean</p><p>5. C. Beautiful</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>I hope its usefull!</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "w-o-b-l-i-n-g-a-good-word-is-tolong-dijawab-cepat-jangan-813",
            "question": "W-O-B-L-I-N-G . A good word is \u2026 *\r\nTolong dijawab cepat \r\njangan ngasal ngasal .....\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>ini hurufnya diacak kan?</p><p>kalo disusun jadinya <strong>bowling</strong><strong>,</strong><strong> </strong><strong>blowing</strong></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "it-is-my-pavourite-pet-it-likes-eating-vegetable-it-has-long-ea-126",
            "question": "It is my pavourite pet. It likes eating vegetable. It has long ears\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>jawaban :</strong></p><p></p><p>rabbit......</p><p></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>It is rabbit </p><p></p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p>Kelinci memiliki 2 telinga yang panjang dan suka memakan sayuran atau tumbuhan hijau itu sudah menjadi makanan pokoknya.</p><p></p><p>See you at the next asnwer </p><p>Pawuuu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "26-rio-do-you-still-have-a-seat-for-the-afternoon-flight-lita-148",
            "question": "26. Rio : \"Do you still have a seat for the afternoon    flight\r\nLita :\"Let me see. Is Qantas OK?\"\r\nRio \"I prefer Garuda if it is available.\"\r\nWhat is the man doing?\r\nA He is having a meeting\r\nB. He is asking a seat\r\nC. He is reserving a ticket\r\nD. He is flying with Garuda.\r\nE He is sitting down for afternoon tea.\r\nDesi\r\n\"Do you mind if I use your pen to sign\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p></p><p>C. he is reserving a ticket.</p><p></p><p></p><p>cmiiw</p><p></p><p>*kalau tepat, jadikan jawaban brainliest ya</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "9-the-purpose-of-the-text-is-a-entertain-the-readers-b-de-356",
            "question": "9. The purpose of the text is ...?    a. Entertain the readers\r\nb. Describe something\r\nc. Tell past event\r\nd. How to make something\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>textnya mana cuy</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>gaada textnya mas</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>kalau bisa teksnya di sertakan</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "how-did-you-say-to-compare-animal-433",
            "question": "How did you say to compare animal",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Bagaimana Anda mengatakan untuk membandingkan hewan</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>tuh artinya</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>adalah hai</p><p> kamu namanya siapa</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "my-house-i-am-nisa-i-live-in-patokbeusi-my-house-is-at-no-40-j-280",
            "question": "My House    I am Nisa. I live in Patokbeusi. My house is at no. 40 Jl. Raya Patokbeust. It's not big house\r\nIt's medium. It's painted grey. It has two floors. I like it anyway. It has a small garden and palm\r\nand mango tree in front of the house. It has looks green and nice\r\nMy house has four bedrooms, two living rooms, a dining room, a kitchen and two\r\nbathrooms. My bedroom is in the front part of the house, next to the living room. My parents' room\r\nis in the middle part of the house next to the dining room. The kitchen and the bathroom are at the\r\nback part of the house. I love house\r\nvery\r\nmuch\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>ngelek ngelek jaringan telkomsel macam tai</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1-write-a-personal-letter-and-the-structure-of-the-letter-comple-772",
            "question": "1. Write a personal letter and the structure of the letter completely.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>saya tidak bisa mafaat saya tidak bisa mafaat saya tidak bisa mafaat</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}